<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <NT_ToyThrumbo.label>Toy Thrumbo</NT_ToyThrumbo.label>
  <NT_ToyThrumbo.description>A thrumbo that stopped growing at dog size, even in adulthood. Centuries of selective breeding made it far more fragile than normal thrumbos, but in return it became incredibly endearing. Most importantly — it produces zero filth!</NT_ToyThrumbo.description>
  <NT_AcidThrumboRace.label>Acid Thrumbo</NT_AcidThrumboRace.label>
  <NT_AcidThrumboRace.description>A unique thrumbo subspecies completely immune to toxins. Its bites and headbutts inject lethal poison.</NT_AcidThrumboRace.description>
  <NT_SwampThrumbo.label>Swamp Thrumbo</NT_SwampThrumbo.label>
  <NT_SwampThrumbo.description>A thrumbo dwelling in wetlands and marshes. Extremely aggressive, alternating rapid horn stabs with powerful axe-like tail strikes.</NT_SwampThrumbo.description>
  <NT_AuroraThrumboRace.label>Aurora Thrumbo</NT_AuroraThrumboRace.label>
  <NT_AuroraThrumboRace.description>A legendary thrumbo adapted to extreme cold. Its fur shimmers with aurora-like luster. Does not destroy trees, produces very little filth.</NT_AuroraThrumboRace.description>
  <NT_FireThrumboRace.label>Fire Thrumbo</NT_FireThrumboRace.label>
  <NT_FireThrumboRace.description>A rare thrumbo dwelling in lava wastes and extreme deserts. Highly resistant to heat and fire, producing a steady supply of chemfuel.</NT_FireThrumboRace.description>
  <NT_DesertThrumbo.label>Desert Thrumbo</NT_DesertThrumbo.label>
  <NT_DesertThrumbo.description>A thrumbo subspecies adapted to harsh desert environments. Can withstand prolonged starvation, but prone to violent retaliation when taming fails.</NT_DesertThrumbo.description>
  <NT_PrairieThrumbo.label>Prairie Thrumbo</NT_PrairieThrumbo.label>
  <NT_PrairieThrumbo.description>A thrumbo with a thick bone dome on its head. Speed comparable to humans, but extremely high defense. Dome can be harvested when butchered.</NT_PrairieThrumbo.description>
  <NT_JungleThrumbo.label>Jungle Thrumbo</NT_JungleThrumbo.label>
  <NT_JungleThrumbo.description>A thrumbo adapted to jungle environments. Periodically produces herbal medicine, but due to plant-like physiology, fire is its fatal weakness.</NT_JungleThrumbo.description>
</LanguageData>